翻译  草草
时间轴  Kallen
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
第四季  第七集
纸牌屋
人人影视倾情奉献
邓巴退出竞选
安德伍德成为仅剩的民主党候选人
哈里发国占领了库尔德要塞
艾德华·H·密查姆
威尔·康威正在进行网络直播
康威直播大热
波利跳流量激增
波利跳搜索趋势
康威红爆网络
...支持我改革民主党的努力
...supporting my efforts to reform the Democratic Party...
恢复总统办公室的正直
and to restore integrity to the Oval Office.
很遗憾
Unfortunately,
我将无法完成我期望达成的目标
I won't be able to complete the work I set out to achieve.
显然  我的竞选已经成了
It has become clear that my candidacy has become
闹剧而非出路
a distraction rather than a solution...
争议已经盖过了问题
that controversy has trumped the issues.
因此  我将结束
And for that reason, I am ending my bid...
对民主党总统候选人的竞选
...to be the Democratic nominee for president.
以上是希瑟·邓巴在华盛顿的竞选总部发表的讲话
That was Heather Dunbar from her campaign headquarters in Washington.
邓巴退出后  安德伍德总统
With Dunbar out, that leaves President Underwood
将成为预计提名人
as the presumptive nominee.
现在的焦点  是安德伍德总统将与谁...
The focus now is on who President Underwood's running--
早上好
Good morning.
妈妈
Mommy?
你好  亲爱的
Hello, darling.
-我想吃早餐  -你想吃早餐
- I want breakfast. - You want breakfast?
-爸爸呢  -他在准备上班
- Where's Daddy? - Oh, he's getting ready for work.
我要给你剪头
I'm gonna cut your hair.
-不不不  -我要给你剪头
- No! No! No! - I'm gonna cut your hair.
-不不不  -为什么说"不"啊
- No! No! No! No! - What do you mean "No"?
不
No!
我要把你剪成小秃子
I'm gonna make you a little bald boy.
不  剃妈妈的头  别剃我的
No! No, shave Mom's head, not mine!
剃妈妈的头  好吧
Shave Mom's head? Okay.
-不  不  -我来剃妈妈的头
- No! No! - I'll shave Mom's head.
-不  -我来剃妈妈的头
- No. - I'll shave Mom's head.
我们最近太急了
We've been moving so quickly.
或许该退后一步  好好考虑一下
Maybe we should take a step back. Think this through again.
我们不能跟彼此别扭  克莱尔
We can't afford to be weird with each other, Claire.
别扭  什么意思
Weird? What do you mean?
我在厕所里看到你了  那么看着我
I saw you in the bathroom... looking at me.
不是第一次了
It's not the first time.
有时候我想说些话  却不知该说什么
Sometimes I want to say something, I just don't know what to say.
-这很不舒服  -或许会永远如此
- It's uncomfortable. - Maybe it will always be like that.
但我们得排除那些  不能让它影响我们的计划
But we have to separate that out. It can't affect our plan.
因为这是唯一
Because that's the one thing...
我们已经想明白了的
that we have figured out.
沃克和瓦斯奎兹
When Walker and Vasquez...
背叛我们
betrayed us,
把说好给我的国务卿给了别人时
pulled the Secretary of State right out from under my feet,
当时不容我们有疑虑  是你提醒了我
there was no room for doubt, and you made me remember that.
我们走上了一条路
We took a path...
一条艰难的路
a difficult one,
因为完全无法保证这条路会通往何方
because we had no guarantee where it was going to lead us.
那需要莫大的勇气
It took a steel goddamn stomach,
自此之后我们不得不做的一切都是如此
and so has everything else we had to do since.
所以现在别去担心你和我
So don't worry about you and me now.
找到你的勇气  克莱尔
Find your steel, Claire.
感谢大家前来
Thank you all very much for coming.
你看到这个了吗
Have you seen this?
哈里发国  哈里发帝国组织
ICO. Islamic Caliphate Organization.
领袖是艾哈迈德和尤瑟夫·艾哈迈迪
Ahmed and Yusuf Al Ahmadi.
他们一直精明地分开行动
They've been smart about keeping split up.
万一一个死了  另一个就接管
If one dies, the other takes over.
但他们要在北叙利亚召开策划会议
But they're holding a planning session in northern Syria.
现在两人都在那里
Both are there right now.
约旦河谷的事我被整得很惨
I got my ass handed to me over the Jordan Valley.
我不能批准发动导弹袭击
I'm not gonna launch a missile strike
除非我相信国家安全受到严重威胁
unless I believe that there's an overwhelming national security threat,
而我不认为他们构成这种威胁
and I'm just not convinced that they pose one.
总统认为哈里发国是严重威胁
The president believes ICO to be a serious threat.
我们认为他们在积极地招募美国民众
We believe they are actively recruiting American citizens.
因此  政府要申请
Accordingly, the government is requesting
在主干网上拦截电话和网络流量
702章上游监控令
a Section 702 upstream surveillance order.
-国内监控  -监控流量  不是个人
- Domestic surveillance. - Monitoring traffic, not individuals.
上前
Approach the bench.
外国情报监视法法庭  机密判决的闭门的
The FISA Court. Classified rulings behind closed doors.
就连他们都不知道我们今早派去了律师
Not even these men know we have a lawyer in there this morning.
哈里发国已经控制了三个油田
ICO already has three oil fields under their control.
俄罗斯减产时
They made a fortune selling crude
他们靠卖原油大挣了一笔
when Russia cut down production.
这是间接后果  先生  我们有责任做出回应
It's blowback, sir. It's our responsibility to address it.
如果我们发动袭击  只会让更多极端分子疯狂
If we launch strikes, we radicalize even more extremists.
先生  他们的军队会壮大的
Sir, their army will grow.
艾哈迈迪兄弟是前复兴社会党党员
The Ahmadis are former Baathists
有很硬的生意关系
with strong business ties.
如果现在出击  可以趁他们还没壮大砍下它的头
We can cut the head off before they get bigger if we strike now.
如果威胁等级提升  我们再重新考虑
If the threat level increases, we'll reassess.
先生  我们时机有限
Sir, we have a very limited window.
将军  总统已经决定了
General, the president's made his decision.
非常感谢  二位先生
Thank you very much, gentlemen.
我是批过一些比较过分的申请  史蒂夫
I have rubber-stamped some borderline requests, Steve,
-但这也  -我知道
- but this is very-- - I know.
我也觉得惊讶
I was surprised, too.
但这是直接来自白宫的意思
But it's straight from the White House.
这得要点时间了
Well, this is going to take some time.
我得好好审核一下
I have to do a proper review.
这把枪是一个职业罪犯非法地
This gun was illegally obtained by a career criminal
在一个不强制背景审查的枪展上购得的
at a gun show where background checks aren't mandatory.
这把枪在一次常规交通违章处理中
This gun killed Officer Dempsey's partner
打死了邓普西警官的搭档
at a routine traffic stop.
这把是在网上购得  完全没有背景审查
This one was ordered on the Internet. No background checks.
这把枪打死了鲍勃和苏·格兰特14岁的儿子
This gun killed Bob and Sue Grant's 14-year-old son.
这是打死了艾德华·密查姆特工的那把枪
And this is the gun that killed Agent Edward Meechum.
没几个特勤局特工能葬在阿林顿国家公墓
Not many Secret Service agents buried at Arlington.
我认为这是他应得的
I'd say he earned his place.
我没有意识到  他对我是多么重要
I took it for granted, how important he was to me,
我多么依赖他
how much I leaned on him.
现在他死了  我才看明白
It's clear to me now, now that he's gone.
我不想对你犯同样的错误  唐纳德
I don't wanna make the same mistake with you, Donald.
什么意思
How do you mean?
我之前没意识到我多么倚重你
I didn't realize how much I lean on you.
我中枪之后  你应对一切的手腕
The way you handled everything after I was shot,
堪称大师
it was masterful.
我...也就是勉强维持吧
Well, I... I guess I kept my head above water.
克莱尔跟我说了你给予了多大的支持
Claire told me how supportive you were,
证明了自己是怎样一位天生的领导者
what a natural leader you proved to be.
我想要这样的人留在身边  唐纳德
I want that by my side, Donald,
就像密查姆生前那样  我想要你做我的竞选搭档
the same way that Meechum was, as my running mate.
你要我做竞选搭档
You want me on the ticket?
据总统只有一步之遥  现在得严肃对待了
A heartbeat away from the presidency is a serious matter now.
康威是个不好对付的对手
Conway is a tough opponent.
我没想到你会想要我
I never expected you'd want me.
我以为我只是个占座的
I thought I was just a placeholder.
不  我们能赢的  唐纳德  你和我联手
No, we can win, Donald. You and I, together.
这行吗  弗兰克
I don't know, Frank.
你需要一个对此十分渴求的人
You need someone who's hungry for this.
我不是很会竞选
I'm not a great campaigner.
-佛蒙特州帮不上你  -你有很深的责任感
- Vermont doesn't help you. - You have a deep sense of duty,
就像这里埋葬的所有为国捐躯的男男女女
like all the men and women here who served their country,
这对我来说比策略重要多了
and that's far more important to me than strategy.
老实说  我不知道我是不是想要  弗兰克
To be honest, I don't know if I want it, Frank.
我接手的时候  那份压力  责任
When I had to take over, the stress, the responsibility...
两周的总统已经是我的承受极限了
Two weeks as president was about as much as I can handle.
我好失望  唐纳德
I'm disappointed, Donald.
但我理解
But I understand.
我不会逼迫你
And I won't pressure you.
我们开始吧
Should we do this?
好了
Okay.
如果不是我  你有其他人选吗
Do you have other folks in mind, if it isn't me?
我们或许该联系一下领导层
Well, we should probably reach out to the leadership,
询问他们的意见
and get their advice.
但你是对的
But you're right.
不管是谁  得是一个对此十分渴求的人
Whoever it is, they need to be hungry for it.
这些死亡本都可以避免
All of these deaths could have been prevented.
因此
And that's why
我在跟一个参议员联盟合作  出台一部法律
I'm working with a coalition of senators to introduce a law
对所有枪支交易都进行背景审查
that will extend background checks to all gun transactions,
包括枪支展和在线销售
including gun shows and online sales.
我想说清楚  这不是针对枪支持有的打击
And let me be clear, this is not an assault on gun ownership.
而是对非法持有枪支的打击
It's an assault on illegal gun ownership.
我现在将回答问题
I'll now take questions.
有请下任美国总统
The next President of the United States,
我的挚爱  一个母亲最好的伴侣
the love of my life, the best father a mother could hope for,
我丈夫  威尔·康威
my husband, Will Conway.
康威  康威  康威
Conway! Conway! Conway!
纽约  你们好
Hello, New York!
他在所有战场州都以两位数领先
He's ahead by double digits in every battleground state.
共和党全国委员会筹集了我们两倍的钱
The RNC is raising two-to-one what we have.
-这人是个摇滚明星  -我们需要自己的摇滚明星
- This guy is a rock star. - We need our own rock star.
您在考虑谁  总统先生
Who are you thinking of, Mr. President?
唐纳德·布莱斯
Donald Blythe.
您不觉得有策略上更好的选择吗
Uh, don't you think there's a more strategic choice?
这就是出于策略考虑
I am being strategic.
邓巴退出是一码事
Look, it's one thing that Dunbar's dropped out,
但我们得拉拢她的支持者
but we have to get her supporters.
唐纳德·布莱斯一身清廉
And Donald Blythe, he oozes integrity.
他可以帮我们把那些
He can help us get all of those
幻想破灭的选民拉回我们的阵营
disillusioned people back into our camp.
大选中的温和派呢
What about moderates in the general?
我们需要一个来自摇摆州的人
We need somebody from a swing state.
而且有殷实的筹款途径
With deep fundraising pockets.
我们可以拿唐纳德的经验做卖点
Well, look, we can sell Donald's experience.
他已经替过班
He's filled the shoes.
为什么要半途换马啊
I see no reason to change horses midstream.
他的资质不够多
He doesn't check off enough columns.
我们需要个斗士  而不是个教授
We want a fighter, not a professor.
我同意  先生  我们能找到比布莱斯更好的
I agree, sir. We can do better than Blythe.
我实在想不出还有谁比
Well, I am hard-pressed to come up with anyone better
真正坐在过那张桌子后面的人更有资格
than a man who actually knows what it's like to sit at that desk.
我们可以给您提几个名字
We can offer you some names.
-他会很难过的  -我去跟他谈
- He'll be devastated. - Let me talk to him.
不  还是我来  我去找他谈吧
No, it's better that I do. Let me talk to him.
我们马上给您准备名单
We'll get you that list right away.
好吧  如果你能想到其他人选
Well, all right. If you can come up with some alternatives,
我绝对愿意听听  多谢各位
I'm certainly willing to listen. Thank you all very much.
我认为最好的政府  是职权最有限的
And I believe the best government is that which governs least.
这并非新的思想  而是个老的
That's not a new idea. It's an old one.
是我党创始人  杰弗逊说的
The founder of our party, Jefferson, said it.
我们得赋予它新生
We need to make it new again.
我们需要一个不干扰人民生活的政府
We need a government that doesn't interfere with people's lives,
不打扰他们的自由  他们对幸福的追求
with their liberty, with their pursuit of happiness.
这不正是我们需要保护的吗
Isn't that what we need to protect?
是的
Yes.
而这正是安德伍德总统最让我们失望之处
And that's where President Underwood is failing us the most.
道格  那个进展...
Doug, where are we on the, uh--
外国情报监视法法庭还得要一阵  法官不太情愿
FISA Court could take a while. The judge was reluctant.
我还是应该安排一次会面
I should set up a meeting anyway.
我一直不喜欢这个计划  先生
I've never liked this plan, sir.
我觉得拿到法庭裁决之前我们不该妄动
I don't think we should do anything until we get the court ruling.
A计划已经启动了  我们先看看结果吧
Plan A is in motion, let's let that pan out first.
如果A计划成功  那么波利跳就不是问题了
If plan A works, then fine, Pollyhop is no longer a problem,
但如果不成功  我得开始打基础了
but if it doesn't, I need to start laying the groundwork.
-麦卡伦没那么好说服  -我们不了解此人
- Macallan could take some convincing. - We don't know this man--
我们现在并不非得扩大圈子
Yeah, we don't absolutely need to widen the circle right now.
是非得  先生
We do, sir.
光是启动这样的监控行动就得要好几周
Just to get this sort of surveillance operational can take weeks.
但道格说得对
Yeah, but Doug is right.
我们不了解他  他对我们是个陌生人
We don't know him. He's a stranger to us.
他是国内  或许是全世界最棒的数据科学家
He is the top data scientist in the country, maybe the world.
-他曾研究行为浸染...  -行了
- He was exploring behavior adoption and immersing... - Stop.
这可是国内监控  莉安
We are talking domestic surveillance, LeAnn.
我唯一在乎的理论就是风险和票数的比例
And the only theory I'm interested in is risk versus votes.
他能帮我们拉到票
And he gets us the votes.
您没听到领导层的话吗
Didn't you hear the leadership?
他们说康威要把我们灭掉了
They said Conway is destroying us.
麦卡伦能逆转这一点  他能帮我们拿下选举
Macallan reverses that, he wins us the election.
"哈里发国占领了库尔德要塞"
"ICO occupies Kurdish stronghold."
有多少人听说过哈里发国
How many of you have heard of ICO?
他们是穆斯林极端分子  在叙利亚攻占油田
They're Muslim extremists taking over oil fields in Syria.
媒体对他们几乎鲜有报道
The media is barely covering them
就因为白宫对此睁一只眼闭一只眼
because the White House is turning a blind eye.
作为纽约州长
As the Governor of New York...
我无法对恐怖主义视而不见
I can't turn a blind eye to terrorism
因为它曾发生在我们家门口
because it's been right here on our doorstep.
知道911发生时我做了什么吗
You know what I did when 9/11 happened?
我加入了空军  因为我想为国尽忠
I joined the Air Force because I wanted to serve my country,
就像我祖父那样
just like my grandfather did
他当年就在这个码头登上了一艘运输舰
when he boarded a transport ship on this very dock
前往太平洋  与日本人作战
and sailed to the Pacific to fight the Japanese.
等我的孩子长大了
When my children grow up...
查理和莉莉
Charlie and Lily...
我希望我能看着他们的眼睛
I wanna be able to... to look them in the eye...
告诉他们  我曾为你们而战
and tell them that I fought for you.
我曾为你们的未来而战
I fought for your future.
在我看来  那个未来很明确
And to me, that future is clear.
就是小政府  减税收
Less government, less taxes,
更加自由  保护自由
more freedom, protect that freedom!
非常感谢  谢谢  谢谢
Thank you so much. Thank you, thank you.
州长  能否说说您和搜索引擎
Governor, can you comment on your relationship
波利跳的关系
with the search engine Pollyhop?
波利跳是否真的在向您提供选民数据
Is it true Pollyhop is providing you with voter data?
-马上把格兰特叫来  -他好像在加州
- I want Grant here, right away. - Uh, he's in California I think.
他有两架私人飞机  选一架飞过来
He's got two Gulf Streams. Have him pick one.
非常感谢  谢谢你  保重
Thank you so much, thank you. Thank you, take care.
波利跳是否真的在向您提供选民数据
Is it true Pollyhop is providing you with voter data?
-提问被人拍下了  -他回应了吗
- The question was caught on camera. - Did he answer it?
没有  网上已经有很多关注了
No. It's getting a lot of traction online.
到早上应该报道满天飞了
Should be all over the news by morning.
让赛斯把目前为止的报道和简报都拿给我
Have Seth send me all the stories and clips so far.
我觉得我现在不需要去见莉安的人
I don't think I have to meet LeAnn's guy now.
-A计划会好使的  -不不
- Plan A's gonna work. - No, no, no.
去见他  这并不能定下来什么
Meet with him. Look, it doesn't commit us to anything.
-先生  -听着  我跟你一样也不想走这条路
- Sir- - Look, I don't wanna go down this route any more than you do,
但至少也算面面俱到了
but at least we'll have our bases covered.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
想象一个决斗在我和康威之间展开
Imagine a duel. Me and Conway.
康威有一把厉害的枪  一个搜索引擎
Now, Conway has a powerful gun, a search engine.
之所以厉害  是因为靠它
And it's powerful because with it,
他就能知道你在想什么  你想要什么
he can tell what you think, what you want,
你在哪  你是谁
where you are and who you are.
他可以把这些搜索都变成票
He can turn all those searches into votes,
这些子弹足够打死我的胜算
and that's enough bullets to kill my chances of winning.
但我有把更大的枪  叫做国家安全局
But I have an even bigger gun. It's called the NSA.
这就是做总统的优势之一
It's one of the perks of being president.
如果法庭批准我进行监控的话
That is, if the courts allow my surveillance request.
我猜挂在这墙上的男人
I imagine the men hanging on these walls
也希望他们当时有那样的一把枪
wished they'd had a gun like that available to them.
你的手机  你身旁那个人的手机
Your phone, the phone of the person sitting next to you,
你邻居的手机  你认识的每个人
your neighbor's phone and everyone you know
和你不认识的三亿美国人
and the 300 million Americans you don't know.
我能看到你  我能用我所见  操纵这次选举
I can see you, and I can use what I see to rig this election.
当然  这样的武器
Now, of course, a weapon like that,
可以想见  风险有多大
well, you can imagine how risky it is.
可能他那样的老坏蛋都会觉得犹豫呢
Huh, it might have even given pause to an old crook like him.
就因为监听了水门大厦的
I mean, they roasted him on the spit
几个房间  他就被人吊打
for tapping into a few rooms at the Watergate.
我可是要监听每一个美国家庭
I'm talking about tapping into every single home in America.
这样的武器  有可能在我手中爆炸
And a weapon like that could blow up in my hand
所以这是B计划  A计划要安全得多
and that's why it's plan B. Plan A is much safer.
曝光康威在违法使用他的枪
Expose that Conway is using his gun illegally
将他的武器从他手中夺下
and remove the weapon from his hand.
我们三个都挨过子弹
All three of us took bullets.
我知道我们为什么要笑  我们活下来了
Well, I know why we're smiling. We survived.
艾丹  这位是道格·斯坦普
Aidan. This is Doug Stamper.
嗯  我知道他是谁
Yeah, I know who he is.
为什么找我来
Tell me why I'm here.
国内监控  我们要赢下一场选举
Domestic surveillance. We need to win an election.
-你认真的吗  -如果是呢
- You serious? - What if we were?
国安局
The NSA...
-你愿冒这样的险  -如果你值得信任
- You'd take that risk? - If you can be trusted.
你的每一条理论
Every theory you have ever had,
你想检验的一切
everything you have ever wanted to test.
作为回报  你得到什么
And in return, you get what?
选民数据  好知道该针对谁
Voter data? So you know who to target?
以及如何找到他们  影响他们
And how to target them, to influence them.
给他们洗脑吗
To brainwash them?
这是为了康威  波利跳的事
Oh, this is about Conway, the Pollyhop thing.
-我就不该告诉你的  -我们是在浪费时间吗
- I never should've told you that. - Are we wasting our time?
我不能安排任何人去做
I couldn't put a single person on this.
-不  这太危险  -谈话结束
- No. It's radioactive. - We're done.
-到此为止  -要怎么做啊
- This is over. - How would this even work?
获得主干网权限...
To get backbone access requires--
我们在争取一个外国情报监视法判决  反恐
We're getting a FISA ruling, counter-terrorism.
我从未在国安局中过标
I've never won a bid from the NSA--
-莉安  我们走吧  -你能赢
- LeAnn, let's go. - You'd win the bid.
这就是你想要的  艾丹
This is what you want, Aidan.
老天
Jesus.
你来是想看能不能信任我
You came here to see if you can trust me.
我怎么知道我能信任你
How do I know I can trust you?
我不在乎你是不是信任我
I don't care whether you trust me or not.
但如果我们走上这条路
But if we go down this road,
万一出事  你得背锅
you take the fall if anything goes wrong.
不是我们  不是总统  是你
Not us, not the president. You.
只能这样
It's the only way this works.
告诉我你觉得是不是值得
So you tell me if you think it's worth it.
价值
The worth.
你根本不了解
You have no idea.
多谢你能来
Thank you so much for coming.
-杰弗里  -州长
- Jeffrey! - Governor.
你怎么样  多谢你
How you doing? Thank you so much.
卖下了一整张桌子  你对我们太好了
Buying a whole table. I mean, you've just been so great to us.
为你什么都行  州长  能合个影吗
Anything for you, Governor. Can I get a photo?
当然
Of course.
你怎么样  里奇
How you doing, Rich?
波利跳的事是真的吗
Is this, uh, Pollyhop thing true?
汉娜也一起拍吧  汉娜
Let's get Hannah in this. Hannah.
-杰弗  -汉娜  见到你真高兴
- Oh, Jeff. - Hannah, good to see you.
-我也是  你怎么样  -格兰特先生来了
- Good to see you. How are you? - Mr. Grant is here.
我很好  你呢
I'm good, how are you?
杰弗里  我回头再找你  我就回来
Jeffrey, I'm gonna come find you, okay? I'll be right back.
-好  -我们拍吧
- Okay. - Let's do it.
我接到了《纽约时报》的电话
I'm getting calls from The New York Times.
这事现在是瞒不住了
There is no way we can keep a lid on this now.
我们接到了来自各方的电话
We're getting calls from everyone.
如果媒体真的深挖
If the media really digs their feet in,
别考虑公众的反应了
forget about the public response.
我们得担心司法部了
We need to worry about the Justice Department.
你说我们的做法并不违法
You said what we're doing wasn't illegal.
不  我说是灰色地带  不受监管
No, I said it was gray, that it's unregulated.
我们的数据是私有的
Our data is proprietary.
我们如何使用  是我们的特权
How we want to use it, it's our prerogative.
如果他们给分享那些数据的利益估价
If they put a value on the benefits of sharing all that data,
肯定要超过所有竞选经费上限
the figure would break all campaign finance caps there are.
这事怎么泄露出去的
How the fuck did this get out?
先生  那名记者不是我们记者团的
Sir? That reporter's not in our press pool.
-我们没给他认证  -那么他为谁工作
- We didn't credential him ourselves. - So, who does he work for?
我们还在努力查证
We're still trying to track that down.
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
我这就给您接通  先生
I'll connect you now, sir.
您在跟总统通话了
You are now on with the president.
我得说  我很失望
I must say, I'm disappointed.
我还希望我们第一次见面会是当面见呢
I was hoping the first time we met would be in person.
-我们见过的  -是啊  对了
- We've met before. - Oh, yes, that's right.
你知道我打来是为什么事  总统先生
You know why I'm calling, Mr. President.
不知道  但我的确读到了一些有趣的文章
No, but I have been reading some curious articles.
你觉得这些报道要多久就会成为主流
How long before you think it becomes mainstream?
你安排了那名记者
You planted that reporter.
我可没有  你是谬赞我了
I did not. You're giving me far more credit than I deserve.
如果你把司法部扯进来
If you bring the Justice Department into this,
我会在滥用职权上对你穷追猛打
I'll come down hard on you for abuse of power,
那对你的伤害不会少于对我的伤害
and that'll hurt you just as much as it hurts me.
我不用  他们跟其他人一样
I won't have to. They read the newspapers,
也会看报纸
just like everyone else.
那你最好拉住他们
Well, then you better hold them back.
我提醒你一下  州长
Let me remind you, Governor,
以防你哪天真当上了总统
in case you do become president one day,
司法部是自主的
the Justice Department is autonomous.
我干涉可是违法的
If I were to intervene, it would be illegal.
就像你抢了联邦应急管理署那次吗
Just like when you raided FEMA?
瞧  全国都想相信你腐败
See, the country wants to believe that you're corrupt,
我会画道线把你和...
and I'll draw a very clear line between you--
你做吧  这事闹得越大越好
Go ahead. The more volume on this, the better.
你提出指控  我就让媒体以事实回应
You hurl accusations, I'll let the press hurl facts.
但你究竟想做什么呢
But what did you really hope to achieve?
我觉得你浪费了时间
I think you've wasted your time.
你真有筹码的时候该打给我的
You should have called me when you had some actual leverage.
但我得说  听到你如此激动真是令人喜出望外
But I must say, it is a treat to hear you so worked up.
多谢了
I do thank you for that.
"华盛顿  杰弗逊  林肯
"Washington, Jefferson, Lincoln.
高个子能当好总统"  我们初遇时你对我说的
Tall men make good presidents." You said that when we first met.
是的  我记得
Yes, I remember what I said.
你当时怕了
You were intimidated.
我并不低估你  州长  但怕你
I don't underestimate you, Governor. But intimidated?
光是海拔和自大可不足以让我害怕
Takes a lot more than height and arrogance to intimidate me.
你赶快回你的律师身边吧
You better get back to all your lawyers.
罗马将军苏拉
When the Roman general Sulla,
大约我现在这年纪时
who was about the same age I am now,
向罗马进军  清除城内叛军
marched on Rome to purge the city of usurpers,
当时血流成河
it was a bloodbath.
他最大的对手是一个叫马吕斯的年轻人
His greatest rival was a young man named Marius,
才26岁
who was just 26 years old.
苏拉杀了他之后
And after Sulla had him killed,
他在广场上举起了他的头
he held up his head in the forum
盯着男孩无光的眼睛说
and looked into the boy's dead eyes
"首先  你得学会摇桨
and said, "First, you must learn to pull an oar.
然后才能掌舵"
Only then can you take the helm."
高压110  低压80  不赖嘛
110 over 80. Not bad.
威尔
Will.
我打给了总统
I called the president.
是个错误
It was a mistake.
好吧
Okay.
听着  我们回楼上去
Look, um... why don't we go back upstairs
筹点钱吧
and collect some money?
好吗  大家都想见你
Okay? Everyone wants to see you.
-走吧  -你会想出对策的
- Let's go. - You'll figure it out.
康威打来了  想跟我做交易
Conway called. He wanted to make a deal.
肯定很有意思吧
I'm sure that was enjoyable.
等司法部插手了
It will be even more so
会更有意思的
once the Justice Department gets involved.
那是...
Is that the, uh...
同款  不是同一个
Same model. Not the actual one.
-特勤局居然允许...  -那个
- Surprised the Secret Service let - Well,
他们拔了撞针
they removed the firing pin.
比我想的要轻
It's lighter than I imagined.
这么小的东西居然能造成那么大的伤害
It's amazing something this small could do that much damage.
我本想明天带上的
I was gonna bring it tomorrow,
但或许太戏剧化了
but I think it might be too theatrical.
要我帮你练习吗
You want me to help you practice?
好
All right.
早上好  安德伍德夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
早上好  梅尔曼女士
Good morning, Ms. Melman.
-不  她叫什么  -茱莉亚
- No, what's her first name? - Julia.
-叫这个  -我们不认识
- Use that. - We've never met before.
让她知道第一夫人是谁
Remind her who the First Lady is.
早上好  茱莉亚
Good morning, Julia.
早上好  安德伍德夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
请坐吧
Please, have a seat.
我们想有包容性
We want to be inclusive.
我们希望全国步枪协会与我们合作让法案通过
We'd like the NRA to work with us on getting this bill passed.
我们在两党都广受支持
We have major support on both sides of the aisle.
那是现在  但今后未必
Well, you do for now, but not for long.
即便是20个孩子死于校园枪击
You can have 20 kids massacred in a school shooting.
公众会愤怒呼吁枪支改革
There's always the usual public outcry, demands for gun reform.
但几个月后  人们就会忘记
But a few months go by and people forget.
这份法案会迅速通过国会
Well, this will move through Congress quickly.
我们在两党都广受支持
We've got major support on both sides of the aisle.
那也不足以抵抗阻挠议事
Not enough to break a filibuster.
我们会把此事拖到大选
We'll drag this out till the election.
我们会阻挠参议院其他所有的法案
We'll tie up every other bill in the Senate.
我跟很多参议员谈过  他们...
Well, I've spoken to a lot of Senators and they--
不  别跟她纠缠那个
No, don't get bogged down there.
把重点直接戳到最高法院
Pivot right to the Supreme Court.
你打算连最高法院提名也拖延吗
You plan on holding up the Supreme Court nomination, as well?
除非你打算提名一位全国步枪协会的成员
Unless you're going to nominate an NRA member.
-你知道那不可能  -雅各布斯不好预测
- You know we can't do that. - Jacobs was unpredictable.
这次我们不会冒险了
This time we're not taking any chances.
如果你让政府停摆
If you bring the government to a standstill,
我们就把全国步枪协会作为选举重点
we're gonna make this election about the NRA.
你拼不过一个亿的广告
You can't match $100 million in ad buys.
去吧  把你的钱都浪费掉吧
Go for it. Flush your money down the drain.
民主党数十年前就输了这场仗了
The Democrats lost that battle decades ago.
你还会再输一次
And you'll lose it again.
总统任党鞭时未提出过一项枪支改革法案
The president never offered up one gun reform bill while he was whip.
因为那当时并非他的首要考虑
Well, because it wasn't a top priority for him--
不不不  更强势点
No, no, no, no, no. Make it, uh, stronger.
比如  "总统挨了颗子弹"  弄成私事
Say, uh, "The president took a bullet!" Make it personal.
我对您丈夫遭枪击感到遗憾
I'm sorry your husband got shot.
但不至于因此妥协
But not enough to roll over.
我们不是叫你妥协
Oh, we're not asking you to.
我们是希望你站在历史正确的一方
We're inviting you to be on the right side of history.
这不错  但你得拿出致命的招数
Yeah, that's good, but you wanna go in for the kill.
我们要这女人气得夺门而出
We want this woman storming out of that door,
口吐白沫
foaming at the mouth.
好吧  别丢人了  茱莉亚
All right. Don't disgrace yourself, Julia.
-想想未来  -不  再强硬点
- Think about the future- - No, tougher.
再狠点  再强硬点
Stronger, tougher!
好吧  那这样如何
All right, what about...
三十年后  当你接受临终护理  奄奄一息时
Thirty years from now when you're dying in hospice care...
你可以回首人生  为你拯救的生命而自豪
you can look back and be proud of all the lives you saved.
也可以被历史遗忘
Or you can be forgotten...
用你冰冷僵硬的双手紧紧抓住过去
clutching onto the past with your cold, dead hands.
我自己出去吧
I'll show myself out.
这就是我说的那份勇气
That's exactly the steel goddamn stomach I was talking about.
是皮特·德雷尔吗
Was it Pete Dreyer?
德雷尔议员是我多年的导师
Congressman Dreyer's been a mentor for years.
-他无权告诉你  -他完全有权
- He had no right to tell you. - He had every right.
如果众议院情报委员会的成员
If a member of the House Intelligence Committee
决定对我透露情报  他有这个权利
chooses to share information with me, he's at liberty to do so.
我们的谈话是私下的
Our conversation was in confidence.
这让我很不舒服
I don't feel comfortable with this.
议员跟你一样觉得不满
The Congressman is just as frustrated as you are,
他找到我是因为想帮忙
and he spoke to me because he wants to help.
我也想帮忙  将军
And so do I, General.
州长  我是名士兵  我不玩政治
Governor, I'm a soldier. I'm not going to play politics.
你对皮特开口的时候就是在玩政治了
You played politics the moment you opened your mouth to Pete.
-你看到我昨天的讲话了吗  -是的
- Did you see my speech yesterday? - Yes, I did.
我都是真心的
I meant every word of it.
你我都曾为我们国家而战
Now, you and I have both fought for our country.
安德伍德可没有
Underwood hasn't.
他根本不懂  不能理解
He has no idea. He doesn't understand.
所以我得当上总统
And that's why I need to be president,
这样我们才能在需要的时候出击
so we can strike when we need to strike.
听着  我可以帮你  但我需要你的帮助
Look, I can help you, but I need your help to do so.
我从未向媒体透露过机密信息  从没有过
I've never leaked classified information to the press. Not once.
我的同事干过  我没有过
My colleagues have. I haven't.
有个更好的办法
There's a better way.
你起初会觉得不太好
You're not gonna like the sound of this at first,
但听我说完  我们是可以回击的
but if you hear me out, we can fight back on this.
-将军  -总统先生
- General. - Mr. President.
收回去吧  我不接受你的辞职
You can take this back. I am not accepting your resignation.
请坐
Please, sit.
我曾在黎巴嫩作战  先生
I fought in Lebanon, sir.
在索马里  波斯尼亚
Commanded troops in Somalia,
两次海湾战争和阿富汗带过兵
in Bosnia, in both Gulf Wars, in Afghanistan.
我不希望我们再在那样的冲突中陷入困境
I just don't wanna see us bogged down in another conflict like those.
哈里发国就是下一个基地组织和塔利班
ICO is the next Al Qaeda and Taliban.
而你辞职不会有任何用
And you accomplish nothing by resigning your commission.
您现在的政策才是毫无用处
We've accomplished nothing with your current policy.
我不禁觉得
You know, I just can't help but think that...
这时机  太巧了
the timing of this, it's just a bit coincidental.
-什么  -康威昨天发表了一番高谈阔论
- Sir? - Well, Conway gave a big speech yesterday.
他把哈里发国吹得很大  是吧
I mean, he made a big meal out of ICO, didn't he?
他应该是意识到了他们多么危险
I suppose he realizes just how dangerous they are.
不知这情报他是从哪得来的
I wonder where he's getting that information.
我不知道  先生
I've no idea, sir.
我从未跟他说过话  我也不会那么做
I've never spoken to the man, nor would I.
那是机密
It's classified.
那么你的话是发自良心
And you're speaking from your conscience.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
良心有种标志性的臭味儿
Conscience has an unmistakable stink to it,
就像生洋葱和早上的口臭
sort of like raw onions and morning breath.
但谎言的臭味儿
But a lie stinks even more
从一个不习惯撒谎的人身上散发出来  格外浓烈
when it's coming from someone who isn't used to lying.
就像臭鸡蛋和马粪
It's more like rotten eggs and horseshit.
-我们多快能采取行动  -您想采取行动吗
- How soon can we move on this? - You want to conduct the mission?
这能避免你辞职吗
Would it keep you from resigning?
我...
Well, I--
我需要你的专业知识和经验
I need your expertise and your experience,
如果两者都告诉我我错了
and if both are telling me I'm wrong,
那么比起我自己  我更相信你的直觉
I'd rather trust your instincts than mine.
现在还有机会吗
Do we still have an open window?
集会将于明晚结束
The gathering is set to end by tomorrow night.
我先去跟参联会主席和国防部长谈谈
Let me talk to the Chairman and the Secretary of Defense
-然后再签署命令  -当然  先生
- before I sign off on the order. - Of course, sir.
将军  跟总统针锋相对  真是勇敢
General, it takes a brave man to stand up to a president.
如果您批准行动  我们就拿不到裁决了
If you authorize the mission, we won't get our court ruling.
哈里发国如果被消灭
There is no way to justify
就不能作为国内监控的理由了
domestic surveillance once ICO is eliminated.
这没关系  媒体压力越来越大
Which is fine, because media pressure is mounting.
康威别无选择  只能跟波利跳撇清关系
Conway has no choice but to distance himself from Pollyhop.
我们不知道结局会如何
We don't know how that's gonna play out.
我可以告诉你们布洛哈特的辞职结局会如何
Oh, I can tell you how Brockhart's resignation is gonna play out.
每个摇摆州30秒的广告
Thirty-second ads in every swing state.
一位功勋卓著的老兵
A decorated war veteran
痛击我们不重视国家安全
pulverizing us for being weak on national security.
波利跳对我们的打击会远胜于布洛哈特
Pollyhop is gonna pulverize us more than Brockhart ever could.
如果康威要忙着应付公众批评就不会了
Not if Conway is busy fighting public outcry.
想想他们已经收集到的数据
Think about the data they have already gathered.
你向我们提出时  说这是没办法的办法
When you sold us this, you said it was going to be a last resort,
而非唯一的办法
not the only resort.
获得监控批准毫无风险
There is no risk in getting surveillance approved.
然后我们要么用  要么不用
Then we either use it or we don't.
但如果您下令打击  先生  我们就没选择了
But if you order this strike, sir, we don't even have the option.
-你见过麦卡伦了  -是  先生
- You've met with him, Macallan. - Yes, sir.
-他值得信任吗  -我真说不准
- So, can he be trusted? - I honestly can't say.
他比您更明白其中的风险
He understands the risks even better than you do.
-我要下令打击  -先生
- I'm gonna authorize the strike. - Sir...
你的人是无名小卒
Your guy's an unknown.
-布洛哈特可不是  -夫人
- Brockhart isn't. - Ma'am...
-我支持弗兰西斯  -给我接国防部长
- I agree with Francis. - Get me the Secretary of Defense.
我叫克莱尔今天一起来
I've asked Claire to join us today
因为这直接与她
because this directly affects
想要通过的法律相关
the legislation she's trying to get passed.
你们竞选搭档的三个首选
Your top three choices for running mate,
都是反对枪支管制说客的朋友
they're all tight with the gun lobby.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood...
你知道这屋里的人都赞同你想要的改革
You know everyone in this room agrees with the reforms you want,
但我们要考虑大选
but we're thinking about the general election,
而跟全国步枪协会交恶可很不明智
and the NRA is a terrible enemy for us to make.
惠特克会关注摇摆州  筹款
Yeah, now Whittaker's gonna focus on swing states, fundraising...
这时我就唱白脸
That's where I'll play the bad cop.
而你唱脸更白的  等我们打乱了他们的阵脚
You play the worse cop. Then when we get them off balance...
你就再重新唱起红脸
You come back in again as the good cop.
没错  所以我就先说
Exactly. So I will start with...
我觉得这些选择发出的讯息很混乱
Well, I feel that these choices send mixed messages.
我们支持枪支改革  他们不支持
We're for gun reform, they're not.
如果竞选搭档两个人都是狂热的枪支管制支持者
If both names on the ticket are gun-control fanatics,
那整个竞选的重点就成了
then the whole election becomes about...
说私事  就像你让我对付梅尔曼那样
Get personal, the way you told me to with Melman.
四个总统里就有一个遭过枪击
One out of four presidents gets shot at.
十个总统里有一个死于枪伤
One out of every ten dies from a bullet wound.
再强势点
Better than that.
我看着艾德华·密查姆就死在我眼前
I saw Edward Meechum die before my very eyes.
-很好  你很幸运  -我很幸运
- Good. You were lucky. - I'm lucky.
数据对这些人来说毫无意义
Statistics don't mean anything to these people.
他们认为这条路只会通往没收
They see this as a one-way road to confiscation.
如果我选择这样的立场会立刻失去席位
I lose my seat in a heartbeat if I take this stance.
-现在我要唱红脸了  -好  博奇说
- Now, this is where I will play good cop. - Okay, so Birch goes,
"我们希望您能考虑全局  总统先生"
"We're asking you to look at the bigger picture here, Mr. President."
你说得对  鲍勃
You're right, Bob.
-克莱尔  -他们说得都对
- Claire! - They're all right. They are.
我跟全国步枪协会的见面并不顺利
My meeting with the NRA did not go well.
他们打算全力以赴地阻挠此事
They're going to fight this tooth and nail.
当然了
Well, of course they are.
而且这项法案很可能不会通过
And... and the chances are the legislation won't pass.
会通过的  因为你们要让法案
Oh, it'll pass. Because you are going to push it
通过参众两院  成为立法
until it goes through both houses and gets on the books.
我们现在虽然获得支持
We may have support now...
但等法案进行表决的时候
But by the time this bill gets onto the floor...
你就专注于法案措辞吧  议员
You focus on the language, Congressman.
把说服美国人民交给我们
Leave convincing the American people to us.
如果你愿意在法案上与我们合作
Now, if you wanna work with us on this bill,
我就能容忍一个爱枪的候选人
I can stomach a gun-friendly candidate.
你呢  弗兰西斯
What about you, Francis?
致命杀
The kill.
只有一个条件  克莱尔
Only on one condition, Claire.
我不希望我们为法案通过忙里忙外
I don't want us to work our asses off getting this bill passed
却在法院被否决
just to see it knocked down in the courts.
这事我们无从控制  先生
We don't have any control over that, sir.
我们还得找人接替雅各布斯呢
We still need to fill Jacobs' seat.
如果你能找到反枪法官
If you can confirm an anti-gun justice,
我就让爱枪人士做竞选搭档
I'll put a gun-lover on the ticket.
大选期间确认最高法院提名
A Supreme Court confirmation in the middle of an election?
拜托  有点胆子  鲍勃
Oh, come on, grow a pair, Bob.
我们都随你的心了  也满足我们一下嘛
We're giving you what you want. Give us what we want.
你在考虑谁
Who are you thinking about?
没人跟你来吧
Nobody followed you?
没人  我确定
No one. I'm positive.
有时候我会觉得我的学生不对劲
You know, sometimes I have a student and something seems off.
上大学有点太老了  知道吗
They look a little too old, you know? To be in college.
-那是什么  -阿普唑仑[镇静剂]
- What is that? - Xanax.
卢卡斯来过
Lucas came up here.
来校园
To the campus.
他求我帮忙  我拒绝了
He wanted my help and I said no.
如果我答应了  或许他...
Maybe if I had, he wouldn't have...
太傻了
So stupid.
他出来了
He got out.
为什么要那么做
Why did he do this?
这就是我想查明的
That's what I'm trying to find out.
都是真的  汤姆
It's all true, Tom.
-你怎么知道  -我就是知道
- How do you know? - Because I know.
卢卡斯没在遗书中提到你
Lucas didn't mention you in his suicide letter.
肯定是为了保护我
I'm sure it was to protect me.
如果你有任何证据  现在就该拿出来了
If you have any proof, now's the time to share it.
如果我有  你觉得还会发生这样的事吗
If I did, do you think any of this would've happened?
-你可以公开声明  -我签了宣誓书
- You could go on record- - I signed an affidavit.
我现在说什么都一文不值了
Anything I say now is worth shit.
或许就因为这个他们才没再来找我
That's probably why they've left me alone.
不不  别再吃药了
No, no. No. No more pills.
-答应我你会小心  -我保证
- Promise me you'll be careful. - I promise.
如果可以帮忙  我会的
I would help if I could, I--
你就好好照顾自己就行
You just focus on taking care of yourself.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
我能说服你改主意吗
Is there anything I can do to make you reconsider?
是  先生  我理解
Yes, sir, I understand.
我也对发动打击感到高兴
I'm pleased the strike's on, as well.
多谢提醒  再见
Thank you for the heads up. Bye.
该死
Fuck!
-怎么了  -他屈服了
- What's wrong? - He caved.
-将军吗  -是的
- The general? - Yes.
爸爸  什么时候开始
Daddy, when is it?
什么时候开始  本
When is it? Ben?
我对这个没把握  威尔  或许我们该取消
I'm not sure about this, Will. Maybe we should cancel it.
我的律师认为这主意糟透了
My lawyers are saying it's a terrible idea.
不是我们  就是司法部
If it's not us, it's the Justice Department.
-我为公司投入了一切  -相信我吧
- I've put everything into this company. - Just trust me on this.
威尔
Hey, Will.
-往我图片分享上放  -嗯
- For my Insta. - Yeah.
笑一个查理
Okay. Smile, Charlie.
笑吧
Smile.
-好了  -真棒
- All right. - Great.
好了
Here we go.
你个小家伙
You little...
过去
Scoot over.
都好了吗
Are we all set?
是的  先生  就等你了
Yes, sir. Ready whenever you are.
开始喽
Here we go.
好
Okay.
准备好了吗  准备好了吗
You ready? You ready?
嗯
Yep.
开始了
Here we go.
美国  你们好  我是威尔·康威
Hello, America. I'm Will Conway,
共和党总统候选人
Republican candidate for president,
这是我儿子查理
and this is my son, Charlie.
跟大家打个招呼啊  查理
You wanna say hi to everyone, Charlie?
打个招呼  打个招呼吧
A little hi. Can we get a little hi?
不吗  就这样了  就这样了
No? That's all we get? That's all we get.
这是我妻子汉娜  我们的小淘气莉莉
And this is Hannah, my wife. And our little rascal Lily.
她已经不小了
Well, she's not so little anymore,
但绝对还是个小淘气
but definitely still a rascal.
是吧  亲爱的
Aren't you, sweetheart?
我们正在我们奥尔巴尼的家中进行网络直播
And we are webcasting from our home here in Albany.
大家可以看到  我们不住在州长府
As you can see, we don't live in the governor's mansion.
我们跟你们很多人一样  住在普通的民居中
We live in a regular house, just like many of you.
这是我们的起居室
And this is our living room.
一切都是汉娜自己装修的
Hannah has decorated everything herself.
除了玩具
Well, except for the toys.
那是孩子们添加的装饰
That's the... That's the kids' addition to the decor.
好多玩具
A lot of toys.
你们很多人都在新闻中看到或听说了
Now, many of you have seen or read in the news
关于我们竞选团队跟搜索引擎波利跳合作的传言
rumors about my campaign teaming up with the search engine Pollyhop,
我今天想跟大家谈谈这些传言
and I'd like to speak to you today about those rumors
因为那根本不是传言
because they're not rumors at all.
是事实  绝对真实
They're facts. One hundred percent accurate.
这位是我的好朋友本杰明·格兰特
And here is my good friend Benjamin Grant.
他是波利跳的创始人
He's the founder of Pollyhop,
他会跟大家讲讲我们的合作
and he's gonna tell you about our partnership.
很多大公司都不参与政治
Well, a lot of big companies stay out of politics.
他们不想得罪人  但波利跳不是如此
They don't want to offend anyone. But not Pollyhop.
我们不遮掩我们的政治立场
We're not shy about who we support,
我们很骄傲能支持威尔·康威
and we're proud to support Will Conway.
他知道这个国家需要什么  将走向何方
He knows what this country needs and where it's going.
好了
Now...
我知道这可能会吓到很多人
I realize this might scare a lot of people.
我们是否知道你的私人信息
Do we know your personal information?
我们是否能看到你们搜索了什么
Can we see what you're searching for?
我们是否在读你们的邮件
Are we reading your emails?
答案是否定的  我们并未追踪个人
The answer is no. We're not tracking individuals.
我们要的是元数据
We're looking at metadata,
宏观浏览规律  搜索潮流  地域特征
large-scale browsing patterns, search trends, regional portraits.
因为本是对的
'Cause Ben is right.
一位总统应该了解他的选区
A president should know his constituents.
而网络是了解的最佳工具
And the Internet is the best tool for that.
我见过数千人  跟很多人握过手
Now, I've met thousands of people and shaken a lot of hands,
但我不可能跟每个人见面
but I can't meet everyone.
这就是我倾听数百万人心声的办法
So this is my way of listening to millions of you.
如果我了解了你们
Now, it's only fair if I get to know you better,
那么你们也该了解我
you should get to know me better.
所以我虽然没有读你们的私人信件
So while I'm not reading your personal correspondence,
我希望你们能查看我的
I want you to have access to mine.
从今日起
So, from this point forward,
我通过这部手机发的邮件  短信
every email, text message, photo, or video
拍摄的照片和视频
that I use on this phone,
你们都能看到  包括我当上州长后的一切
you can see it all, including everything since I became governor.
你们只需要登录我的竞选网站  网址是
Now, all you have to do is go into my campaign website at...
Conway2016.com
Conway2016.Com.
没错  你就能看到链接
That's correct. And you'll find a link right there.
我们的生活就是你的生活
Our life is your life.
你的未来是我们的未来
And your future is our future.
谢谢  天佑美国
Thank you, and God bless America.
-真不错  -是啊  不错
- That was good. - Yeah, that was good.
干得好  干得好
Well done. Well done.
不客气  州长
You got it, Governor.
好了  我们拭目以待吧
All right. Now we wait and see.
他的诚实和坦诚造成了不小的影响
His honesty and openness have made quite an impact,
美国也竖起了耳朵
and America is paying attention.
康威网络直播后三小时内
Just three hours since Conway's webcast,
就有超过两百万人登录了他的网站
over two million people have visited his website...
公众的广泛关注让波利跳点击量暴增
The massive public interest has driven traffic to Pollyhop.Com.
波利跳执行总裁本杰明·格兰特
Pollyhop CEO Benjamin Grant
称搜索量达到了平时的三倍
is reporting three times its normal volume of searches.
手机视频全部上传到了康威竞选网站
All of the cell phone footage is on the Conway campaign website.
有超多的历史影像
There's a ton of archived clips.
有些已经被疯传  包括这段
Some have already gone viral, including this one,
就拍摄于今天早上
filmed just this morning,
画面中是康威和他美丽的妻子汉娜  好嫉妒啊
of Conway with his gorgeous wife Hannah, so jealous,
以及他萌爆的儿子查理
and his totally adorable son Charlie.
剃妈妈的头  别剃我的
Shave Mom's head, not mine!
剃妈妈的头
Shave Mom's head?
-好吧  -不
- Okay. - No!
猜对了  我还是讨厌孩子
You guessed it. I still hate children.
大家根本不在乎自己的隐私
People don't care about their privacy.
他们希望他看
They want him to have access.
他依然违反了竞选经费法规
He's still breaking campaign finance regulations.
但他得到的报道都是正面的
But he's getting good press,
而不是我们所期望的民愤
not the public outcry we had hoped for.
您不能让司法部调查
You can't let the Justice Department investigate.
只会适得其反
It'll backfire on us.
您得取消空袭
What you need to do is call off the air strike.
先生  您已经签署了命令
Sir, you've already signed the order.
飞机都升空了
We've got planes in the air.
我的工作是赢下竞选  我得...
My job is to win a campaign, I need to have--
-我的工作是保护总统  -够了
- And my job is to protect the president. - Enough!
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
走吧  我得跟他谈谈
Go. I need to speak with him.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
当它只是B计划时我还能接受
That I was fine with this when it was just plan B,
但这是国内监控
but this is... domestic surveillance.
我们都不认识这人
I mean, we don't even know this guy.
你说得对  我们不认识他  但我们知道
You're right, we don't know him. What we do know...
如果不采取措施  我们会输
is we'll lose if we do nothing.
他们真美  是吧  康威夫妇
They're beautiful, aren't they? The Conways.
他们的青春  他们的两个孩子
Their youth, their two little children.
这国家爱上了他们
The country is falling in love with them.
他们不会那样爱我们的
They won't fall in love with us like that,
但我们有他们没有的东西
but we have something they don't.
我们愿比任何人都走得更远
We are willing to go one step farther than everyone else.
将军  说句话
General, a word.
我们还有两小时...
We're approximately two hours out--
-中止行动  -总统先生
- Abort the mission. - Mr. President?
-我命令你中止  -但您说
- I'm ordering you to abort. - But you said--
别逼我再说一遍了  也别威胁要辞职
Don't make me say it a third time, and don't threaten to resign,
因为我知道你不会的
because I know you won't,
因为你无法想象做个平民的滋味
because you can't even fathom what it means to be a civilian.
-执行我的命令  -是  先生
- Execute my order. - Yes, sir.
-先生  -已经下令了
- Sir. - It's done.
-先生  -我中止了
- Sir. - I aborted.
这么晚不睡
You're up late.
登录康威的网站  2012年12月31日
Go to Conway's website. December 31st, 2012.
汉娜2012年的最后时刻
Hannah's last moments of 2012.
够了  我在狼吞虎咽呢
Stop, I'm stuffing my face.
你在喂长身体的女孩嘛  小宝宝  你好啊
You're feeding a growing girl. Hello, little baby.
是啊
Yes, I am.
她在像个疯子似的踢我
She's kicking like a maniac, too.
威尔  求你  别拍了
Will, please, stop.
-怎么了嘛  -别拍了
- No, come on. - No.
你有...你粘了点东西
You've got... You have... You have a little something...
当选州长先生
Mr. Governor-elect.
议员先生  见到您很荣幸
Congressman, such an honor to meet you.
-荣幸的是我  -这是我妻子  汉娜
- Well, the honor is mine. - This is my wife, Hannah.
荣幸  这是克莱尔
It's a pleasure. And this is Claire.
你好
Hello.
-几个月了  -快七个月了
- How far along are you? - Almost seven months.
多谢您邀请我们来
Thank you so much for inviting us here.
这对我们太难得了
This is a real treat for us.
很高兴你来了
Well, I'm glad you came.
我以为你今晚要去时代广场呢
I thought you'd be in Times Square tonight.
德卢卡州长最后一年任职了
It's Governor De Luca's last year in office.
我觉得不该抢他的风头
I thought he should have the spotlight to himself.
你太有风度了
Well, that's very classy of you.
而且我不想错过
And I didn't wanna miss the chance to
在华盛顿结交新朋友的机会
make some new friends in Washington.
真是聪明  你见过加勒特了吗
Well, that was a smart idea. Have you met Garrett, yet?
还没呢  先生
No. No, sir.
来吧  女士们  我们就回来
Well, come on. Ladies, we'll be back.
当选总统先生  这是当选州长康威
Mr. President-elect, Governor-elect Conway.
-恭喜  -也恭喜您  先生
- Congratulations. - You, too, sir.
这就是他啊  那个金童  没那么神秘嘛
So here he is, the boy wonder. He isn't a myth after all.
贱民差不多
More like a pariah.
-这里有好多民主党人  -也有不少共和党人
- There's a lot of Democrats here. - Plenty of Republicans, too.
这是弗兰克张罗的
Frank made sure of that.
如果想在国会取得进展
Well, if you wanna push the sludge through Congress,
就得两边都有朋友
it's best to have grease on both sides of the aisle.
抱歉  我得走了  时间要到了
Oh, I'm sorry, I have to go. It's almost time.
-多谢你的服务  -谢谢您  先生
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you, sir.
你真是在911第二天就入伍了吗
So, is it true that you joined up a day after 9/11,
还是只是一种说法
or is that just something you say?
24小时内  对天发誓
Within 24 hours, honest to God.
真是了不起
That's incredible.
我才25  刚从法学院出来
I was 25, just out of law school.
想步入仕途
You want a career in politics
偏巧赶上双子塔的事
and the Twin Towers fall in your lap?
时机简直再好不过
Timing couldn't have been better.
我明白你是怎么获胜的了
Oh, I see how you won.
-他肯定像站在世界之巅  -我无法想象
- Well, he must be on top of the world. - I... I can't imagine.
是吗  你多大  35
Oh, really? How old are you? Thirty-five?
36岁
Thirty-six.
你夜深人静的时候从没想过吗
Oh, you've never thought about it, late at night?
-白宫吗  -还能是什么
- The White House? - What else?
-你呢  -谁没想过
- Have you? - Haven't we all?
我不急  谁知道呢  或许有一日吧
I'm in no rush. Who knows? Maybe, one day.
华盛顿  杰弗逊  林肯  高个子能当好总统
Washington, Jefferson, Lincoln. Tall men make great presidents.
你就好像希望我竞选似的
It's like you want me to run.
天呐  可不  你竞选
Oh, goodness, no. You running?
那对民主党绝对是灾难
That would be a disaster for the Democrats.
-我得去找我妻子了  -十
- I better see my wife. - Ten...
-我也是  -九
- Me, too. - ...nine,
八  七  六  五  四
eight, seven, six, five, four,
三  二  一
three, two, one!
新年快乐
Happy New Year!
-那还是一切开始之前  -是啊
- That was before everything. - I know.
弗兰西斯  你在听吗
Francis, are you there?
我们要灭了他们
We're going to destroy them.
是的
Yes, we are.
2012年12月14日  康涅狄格州纽顿市发生特大枪击案
20名六七岁的小学生被枪杀
事发后奥巴马委任副总统拜登组织特别委员会
推动新枪支控制法案
但经过数月的运作  新法案仍全无机会通过国会
奥巴马大发雷霆  但也束手无策
不久前  奥巴马决定通过行政命令的方式
绕过国会  推动枪支管控
但这样的努力即使成功  影响也非常有限
伊斯兰国出现早期  美国政府和军事机构就向白宫做过汇报
当时奥巴马对这个恐怖组织非常轻视
认为他们是不入流的流寇  并轻蔑地讽刺说
一个中学校队队员穿上洛杉矶湖人队的队衣
也不会就变成科比·布莱恩特
目前包括曾经在奥巴马政府任职的外交专家都认为
如果奥巴马当初及时采取行动  伊斯兰国不会发展到今天这样
如此迅速地扩张成为历史上最危险的恐怖组织
不仅在中东肆虐  也不放过在欧洲和美国发动大规模袭击的机会